Guide to the Edward Weber Allen Papers 1886-1975
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Personal Papers, 1929-1975
  - Subject Files
    - Politics -- Correspondence, Writings, Clippings, circa 1936-1960 (Box 33)
    - Japanese Trip, undated (Box 33)
    - European Trip, 1953 (Box 34)
    - Trips, undated (Box 34)
  - Legislation, undated (Box 34)
  - Appraisal, undated (Box 34)
  - Research Material, undated (Box 34)
  - Clippings
    - Concerning Allen, undated (Box 34)
    - Concerning North Pacific (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 34)
  - Ephemera, undated (Box 34)
  - Unsorted Materials, undated (Box 34-37)